KEMBOI DUNCAN

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

+254 707 510 970

gdan5703@gmail.com

Thika, Kiambu, Kenya

About Me

Always in love with code and design. I like to learn new things every day and challange myself with new projects, translating concepts into visual design by paying close attention to details and convert it into highly interactive experience.

Experience

Beannsofts Limited 2022 - 2022

Junior Front end developer

I was a junior front end developer for 4 months. Most of the tasks I was assigned included: UI/UX design and development for some of the company's projects.

CodeBuffers 2021 - Present

Front End Developer

Some of the tasks I work on include: UI/UX Design and development, code editing and SEO.

Education

2019 - 2023

Gretsa University

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Language

English **——**

Swahili

Expertise

- UI/UX
- visual design

Reference

Serian Paul Maiyani

Code Buffers - CEO

Phone 011 395 3355